Well, all right, then.
(Penny:)Sheldon? What are you doing?
Playing "Super Mario"
on a poorly coded Nintendo 64 emulator.
(Penny:)But why are you doing it on the stairs?
I am a modern-day Napoleon
exiled to the Elba of the staircase...
(Sheldon:)...because Leonard, get this, has a date.
(Penny:)Oh. Oh, well, good for him.
Yeah, but why are you sitting here?
Why don't you go to a movie or something?
(Sheldon:)Alone?
- Yeah, why not?
- What if I choke on my popcorn?
(Sheldon:)Who will administer
the Heimlich maneuver?
(Penny:)- Then don't order popcorn.
- No popcorn at the mov...?
(Sheldon:)Listen to yourself.
- Why don't you go to a coffee shop?
- I don't drink coffee.
(Penny:)They have other things.
- What do they have?
- I don't know. You know, cookies, pastries...
- Pastries such as bear claws?
- Yeah, sure.
I don't like bear claws.